https://www.oakleywoods.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

CA (CA $)
US  (US $)
(US $)
(CA $)
(US $)
Toll free (866) 364-8895
My Account
Orders
Wish list
Track my order(s)
Track my order(s)
Sign inRegister
Email
PasswordForgot your password?
6 Wicket Association
Golf Croquet (*)
6 Wicket American
9 Wicket (Backyard)
6 Wicket Association
Golf Croquet (*)
6 Wicket American
9 Wicket (Backyard)
SECURE TECHNOLOGY
The Croquet Store protects the integrity of your credit card and personal information using the secure SSL encryption methods. This means that these details are only seen by The Croquet Store. The information you provide is used exclusively by The Croquet Store and Oakley Woods to fulfill your request. We do not engage in selling or renting your personal information.
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Oakley Woods Croquet and The Croquet Store know how important your personal information is. We will not rent or sell your personal information. We will only disclose your personal information with your explicit permission. Please feel free to contact us if you have any concerns regarding data security or how your personal information is used.
STILL NOT SURE?
If you are not comfortable sending your credit card details through the Internet, you need only submit the information you want along with a phone number where we may contact you during our normal business hours (Monday - Friday / 8:00 am - 5:00 pm Eastern time zone). You will be contacted by our staff to obtain the final details. You may also place your entire order by phone,
Toll free (866) 849-8635
My account
Sign in
Create account
Gift certificates
ABOUT US
Contact us
Shipping & Returns
© 1992-2020 Oakley Woods Croquet.
